

**Apostolos Gouvalas** Full-stack Web Developer

Full-stack developer with over 6.8 years of experience in PHP, SQL and JavaScript, among other languages. With attention to detail and a passion for problem solving, I am willing to contribute my skills to dynamic and challenging projects.

■ apo.gouv@gmail.com

+30-697 8811 469

cubedesigns.gr

• Thessaloniki, Greece

### SOCIAL

in linkedin.com/in/apostolos-gouvalas

github.com/ApoGouv

≥ stackoverflow.com/users/4861651/cubakos

## **EDUCATION**

## MS in Mobile and Web Computing

2016 - 2018

[ Distinction ]

**International Hellenic University** (Thessaloniki, Greece)

Digital Systems Degree, majoring in "Communication and Network Systems"

2004 - 2013

University of Piraeus - Department of Digital Systems (Piraeus, Athens, Greece)

### **LANGUAGES**

Greek [Native language] English [Proficiency of Michigan & IELTS 7.5] Spanish [A2 in progress]

#### **SOFTWARE & TOOLS**

VSCode, Git, Linux, Windows, cPanel, etc.

### **HOBBIES**

Cycling, Dancing Salsa/ Kizomba, Sudoku, Rock Music

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Full-stack Web Developer

Nov 2017 - Present | Mental Media (former MultiHosting)

- Development of ecommerce websites, with OpenCart, CS-Cart, PrestaShop, WooCommerce, etc., as well as custom functionalities and integrations with ERP programs.
- Website development (portfolios, corporate, personal, etc.) - WordPress, Joomla, etc.
- Company projects WHMCS, Laravel, vBulletin, Joomla, etc.

## Front-end Web Developer

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017 | PSDGator

 Convert design mockups from PSD or AI to valid HTML and CSS or WordPress Themes.

## Full-stack Web Developer

Dec 2015 - Present | Freelance

 Construction of websites, e-shops and custom solutions according to customer requirements

# Front-end Web Developer

Apr 2014 - May 2014 | igraphics.gr

• Created the user interface, based on the supplied graphic mockups, for applications to visualize the results of the 2014 Italian **European Parliament Elections and display** past Italian election results, with valid HTML, CSS and iQuery.

### **CERTIFICATES**

# JavaScript, React, Node.js, PHP, κ.α.

2017 - 2024 | Udemy

Build a Social Network from Scratch:

JavaScript PHP + MySQL

Jan 01, 2019

The Complete Node.js Developer Course (2nd Edition)

Oct 09, 2017

The Complete JavaScript Course:

Build a Real-World Project

Sep 11, 2017

JavaScript Essentials

Aug 14, 2017